directorycentral.com 2011-12-29

# DirectoryCentral.com - Local Business Listings with Networking

**Effective December 15, 2008:**

SocialTerrain, Inc. ("SocialTerrain" or "we") operates SocialTerrain.Com. This Privacy Policy describes SocialTerrain's use and sharing of personally identifiable information (your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number) that Members voluntarily provide to SocialTerrain when they register (also known as "Registration PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION"). The Term "User" refers to a Visitor or a Member. This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered by SocialTerrain, including any SocialTerrain-branded URL (the "SocialTerrain Website"), the SocialTerrain instant messaging service, the SocialTerrain application developer service and other features (for example, music and video embedded players), SocialTerrain mobile services, and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by SocialTerrain in connection with the SocialTerrain Website (collectively, the "SocialTerrain Services"). The SocialTerrain Services are hosted in the United States. 

The SocialTerrain Website is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION from children under 13 years of age. 

From time to time SocialTerrain may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION collection and use practices, the features of the SocialTerrain Services, or technology, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting by SocialTerrain on the SocialTerrain Website. Your continued use of the SocialTerrain Services after SocialTerrain posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If SocialTerrain materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change. 

**COLLECTION AND SUBMISSION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ON SOCIALTERRAIN**

General. When SocialTerrain collects PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting Registration PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to us in order to register as a Member of SocialTerrain. SocialTerrain may also collect PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION from you if you choose to participate in SocialTerrain Services activities like sweepstakes, contests, and surveys, because you want us to furnish you with products, services, newsletters, or information, or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to SocialTerrain for review. 

In addition, SocialTerrain collects other non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type. This data is used to manage and improve the SocialTerrain Services, track usage, and for security purposes. 

SocialTerrain Members may also choose to provide or store non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION in their profiles, including but not limited to date of birth, interests, hobbies, lifestyle choices, groups with whom they are affiliated (schools, companies), videos and/or pictures, private messages, bulletins or personal statements (collectively "Profile Information"). The Profile Information in a Member's profile is provided at his or her sole discretion. 

SocialTerrain Members can change their Registration PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and Profile Information at any time and can control how Visitors, other Members and SocialTerrain communicate with them by controlling their account settings, available within the "Edit Profile" portion of their SocialTerrain profile. Link to Privacy Settings. 

Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that SocialTerrain places on your computer. SocialTerrain uses cookies to identify your Internet browser, store Users' preferences, and determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on the SocialTerrain Services. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services. 

Third party advertisements displayed on SocialTerrain Services may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers (known as "third party cookies"). SocialTerrain does not control these third party cookies and Users of the SocialTerrain Services should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the "Notice" section below for more information on customized advertising on SocialTerrain. A pixel tag is a tiny image inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. SocialTerrain may allow third party pixel tags to be present on SocialTerrain Services for purposes of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection. 

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the SocialTerrain Services 

**NOTICE: SOCIALTERRAIN WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

When you voluntarily provide PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to SocialTerrain, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses SocialTerrain will make of the information to the extent it is being used in a manner that differs from what is allowed pursuant to this Privacy Policy. 

At the time you provide your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, SocialTerrain will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION (See "Choice" below). Except as described in this Privacy Policy, SocialTerrain will not share your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION with third parties unless you have given SocialTerrain permission to do so (See "Use" below). 

SocialTerrain Services may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. SocialTerrain Services may also carry advertisements from other companies. SocialTerrain is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites or other services operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with the SocialTerrain Services or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. Once you leave SocialTerrain Services via such a link, access a third party application (such as widgets) or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION they collect from you. 

SocialTerrain may use cookies and similar tools to customize the content and advertising you receive based on the Profile Information you have provided. Profile Information you provide in structured profile fields or questions (multiple choice questions like "Marital Status," "Education" and "Children") ("Structured Profile Information"), information you add to open-ended profile fields and questions (essay questions like "About Me," "Interests" and "Movies") ("Non-Structured Profile Information") and other non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION about you may also be used to customize the online ads you encounter to those we believe are aligned with your interests. For example, based on your music interests we might display an advertisement to make sure you are advised when your favorite band is coming to town. The information used for this feature does not provide your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION or identify you as an individual to third parties. 

Some of the advertisements that appear on SocialTerrain Services may also be delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION about your visit to or use of SocialTerrain Services, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads your IP address. 

Third party applications (such as widgets) created by third party developers may also be available on the SocialTerrain Services. Third party applications are small bits of software, often with interactivity, that can be installed into Members' profiles or shared with other Users. However, SocialTerrain does not control the third party developers, and cannot dictate their actions. When a Member engages with a third party application, that Member is interacting with the third party developer, not with SocialTerrain. SocialTerrain encourages Members not to provide PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to the third party's application unless the Member knows the party with whom it is interacting. 

**CHOICE: SOCIALTERRAIN WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, SocialTerrain will get your permission before we use the PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION you provide to us in a way that is inconsistent with the purpose for which it was submitted or share your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION with third parties that are not affiliated with SocialTerrain. 

**USE: SOCIALTERRAIN'S USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

SocialTerrain will only use the PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION you provide under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If SocialTerrain obtains PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy. 

In order to locate other SocialTerrain Members that you may already know in the physical world, SocialTerrain allows Users to search for Members using Registration PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION (i.e., full name or email address). SocialTerrain also allows Users to browse for certain Profile Information in order to help connect with Members (i.e., schools and/or companies where Users may have attended or worked). SocialTerrain may also enable Members to publicly display some Registration PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION as an element of their Profile Information if they choose to do so via a profile setting under "Edit Profile." Search engines may index the portion of a Member's profile (including the Profile Information it contains) that is publicly displayed. 

If you have consented to receive promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications from SocialTerrain, SocialTerrain may periodically use your email address to send you such materials related to the SocialTerrain Services, as applicable. If you want to stop receiving such materials from SocialTerrain, you can change your profile settings under "Account Settings," or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

SocialTerrain employees, agents and contractors must have a business reason to obtain access to your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. SocialTerrain may share your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION with those who help us manage or provide SocialTerrain Services' information activities (for example, message board administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses, data processing), or with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes. 

These outside contractors, agents or sponsors may temporarily store some information on their servers, but they may only use your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to provide SocialTerrain with a specific service and not for any other purpose. SocialTerrain may also provide your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to a third party in those instances where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. SocialTerrain also may share your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION with Affiliated Companies if it has a business reason to do so. 

As described in "Notice" above, SocialTerrain may customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the SocialTerrain Website, or may work with outside companies to do so. Your non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and/or Profile Information may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. SocialTerrain prohibits these companies from sharing your non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and/or Profile Information with any third party or from using it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream, number of page views calculated by pixel tags, and aggregated demographic information may also be shared with SocialTerrain's advertisers and business partners. 

There may be instances when SocialTerrain may access or disclose PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION , Profile Information or non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION without providing you a choice in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of SocialTerrain, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of Users of the SocialTerrain Services or members of the public including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if SocialTerrain sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of all or a material part of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, SocialTerrain may transfer your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction. 

When a Member who is located in the European Union chooses to post Profile Information that will be publicly disclosed, that Member is responsible for ensuring that such information conforms to all local data protection laws. SocialTerrain is not responsible under the EU local data protection laws for Member-posted information. 

**SECURITY: SOCIALTERRAIN PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

SocialTerrain uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and credit card information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, SocialTerrain uses reasonable methods to make sure that PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete. 

**ACCESS, REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR CHANGE YOUR PREFERENCES REGARDING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND HOW TO CONTACT SOCIALTERRAIN ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS**

Whenever possible, SocialTerrain Members may review the Registration PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION we maintain about them in our records. We will take reasonable steps to correct any PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION a Member informs us is incorrect. If you are a Member, you can view and change your Registration PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, Member preferences and Profile Information by logging into your account and accessing features such as "Edit Profile" and "Account Settings." 

If you ask SocialTerrain to stop using your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, SocialTerrain will honor that request while retaining any record of your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law. 

If you would like to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy or SocialTerrain's collection and use of your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION please contact SocialTerrain at: 

Email:  
Support@Socialterrain.com

Mail:  
SocialTerrain, Inc  
127 Peachtree Street, STE 500  
Atlanta, GA 30303
